http://www.electronicexpress.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
For you protection, ElectronicExpress.com will not sell, share, or distribute your e-mail address or personal data to anyone without your permission.
When you visit the ElectronicExpress.com Website, we collect information about your visit. We collect your IP address, browser type, domain name, the number of times you visit and what you purchase from us. Except where listed elsewhere in this privacy statement, we keep this information for our internal use; we do not share it with others.The information we collect online is sometimes combined with records we receive from outside sources for our own marketing purposes. We do not share this combined information with any outside parties.
We use cookies to store information between visits to our site. Cookies are a mechanism to remember information about a visitor from one page to another. Web browsers store cookies so that the browser itself can remember some information and then, on request, pass all that information up to the server at one time. We use cookies to remember your name and the contents of your shopping cart. This allows you to leave our site, come back later, and still have the contents of your shopping cart intact.
When you set up an account with ElectronicExpress.com, we ask you for contact information (your name and email address). We use your email address to uniquely identify you.
We use customer contact information from the account form to send you information about our company and to inform you of sales and special offers. Your contact information is also used to contact you should we have questions regarding your orders or to notify you of the status of your order.
If you place an online order, our secure order form requests contact, billing, and financial information (such as your credit card numbers for purchases). Contact information from the order form (email address, name, billing and shipping address, and phone number) is used to send orders and information about our company to you. Your contact information is also used to get in touch with you should we have questions regarding your order or should we need to notify you of the status of your order. The financial information we collect is used ONLY to bill you for products you purchase.
If you place an online order for a DIRECTV system, we may display a separate form asking for your name, installation address, and phone number. As the form states, we send this information to DIRECTV (to pre-activate your service) and to the entity that will install your satellite.
We occasionally run our own online surveys and we ask visitors for contact information (such as email address) and demographic information (such as zip code, age range, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send users information about our company. This information is also used to contact visitors to learn more about specific problems they might have reported or to give them rewards, if such a reward program is part of the survey. The demographic information is used to learn more about the types of people who visit our site.
We may run contests and promotions on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (such as their email address). We use this information to contact the winners and to send visitors information about our company.
In addition, we occasionally participate in third-party contests and promotions. In these instances, contact information is shared with the third parties so they can select winning entries and ship prizes and promotional material to those who enter. Visitors can elect not to share their information with third parties by not participating in these promotions. Visitors who do elect to share information with third parties must contact the third party directly to opt out of receiving future mailings from the third party.
We will cooperate with law enforcement and judicial authorities, and we may provide personally identifiable information to appropriate government authorities upon receipt of a subpoena or court order, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We will fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies activities that we in good faith believe to be illegal.
Links
This site may at times contain links to other sites. ElectronicExpress.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Change/Modify
This site gives you the following options for removing your information from our database, to not receive future communications, or to no longer receive our service.
1. You can send email to info@electronicexpress.com
2. You can send mail to the following postal address:
ElectronicExpress.com
418 Harding Industrial Dr.
Nashville, TN
37211
You can call the following telephone number: 1-888-257-7500
When You Send Email to our Customer Service Department
We allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We read the messages sent in and try to reply to every one. How We Notify You of Changes to our Privacy PolicyWhenever we change our privacy policy, we will post a notice on our website indicating that a new version is available.
We're Sorry
Sorry, your application was denied.
lorem ipsum dolor sit amet
Enter Your Zip Code
Estimate Shipping & Tax:
Apply
AWS Protection Plans
We know you your hard earned money is important to you, so it's our job to make sure you get the most out of your purchase.
Lowest Cost
Longer Terms
Greater Investment
Learn More about AWS »
Delivery & Installation Options
Drop Off
Cras turpis est, feugiat eu metus vel, iaculis tristique sem. Nam pharetra ligula ipsum. Nam tincidunt ut diam posuere bibendum. Nulla condimentum a erat sed dictum. Nunc ante dolor, blandit quis nulla sit amet, laoreet rutrum ante.
Proin commodo dignissim felis, non facilisis metus dictum ac.
Curabitur id enim dui.
In orci magna, porttitor et erat quis, lobortis lacinia nisi.
Threshold
Vivamus consequat eget eros in sagittis. Nam egestas, velit eget commodo volutpat, nulla dolor varius lacus, vel tincidunt orci enim luctus eros. Nunc ultricies velit libero, eu auctor lectus mattis et.
Non porta turpis lacinia eu.
Quisque commodo, quam non iaculis accumsan, diam purus gravida sem, vitae tristique lacus orci vel lectus.
Suspendisse potenti.
Room of Choice
Integer condimentum tincidunt volutpat. Sed id commodo metus. Donec eu turpis elit. Nulla ornare elementum sapien eu facilisis. Proin porta lobortis felis eget pulvinar. Ut finibus diam libero, vitae placerat sem consequat sit amet.
Proin orci dolor, sodales vitae ante et, mollis elementum libero.
Vivamus eget mi at ligula volutpat consectetur.
In hac habitasse platea dictumst.
White Glove
Phasellus ex velit, porta sed turpis nec, facilisis porttitor ante. Sed vitae euismod mi. Fusce nec odio varius, porta tellus vitae, sodales magna. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Vivamus ut eleifend diam. Nulla facilisi.
Aliquam ac nunc urna.
Ut porta, felis nec lacinia mollis, lacus quam consectetur nisi, non tempor mauris ex a mauris.
Nulla eget libero sit amet libero pulvinar dictum.
